







Minsk, BELARUS +375 29 341 62 40 shuliak.leonid@tut.by



Leonid SHULIAK

Frontend DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- REACT/REDUX
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- Material UI
- Git
- Jest

EDUCATION

2005 - 2009

Institute of Entrepreneurial Activity (Commercial activity)

2001 - 2005

Minsk State Automechanical College

COURSES

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021 FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REACT/REDUX/TS)

IT-Incubator

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021FRONTEND DEVELOPER
(JAVASCRIPT)
The Rolling Scopes School

LANGUAGE

ENGLISH PRE-INTERMEDIATE (IN PROGRESS)

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm a person who is addicted to programming. I have experience in creating SPA using React/Redux, JS/TS, HTML/CSS. Now I'm improving my skills and expanding them, learning new technologies. My free time is dedicated to Codewars and becoming familiar with React Native. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer. I'm married, I have two kids. Ready to consider project work and full-time employment.

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2020 - Present

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

Created SPA apps, developed login pages, modal windows, tests, menu and design. Used the following developer technologies: React/Redux/ReduxThunk/RestApi/Axios/ReduxForm/MaterialUI/SCSS etc. Checked the correctness of the code with Unit Tests and used Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application. Used TypeScript for better control of the code in work.

Oct 2010 - Apr 2018 (as an individual entrepreneur 2011 - 2020)

VEHICLE APPRAISER

Appraised automobiles and heavy equipment to determine the cost of repair for an insurance settlement. Assesses auto damage using electronic estimating software, prepares damage repair cost estimates, and photographs damages for documentation. Resolved controversial issues with clients and insurance companies, found compromises to reduce costs.

Led the department of appraisers since July 2013,

Led the department of appraisers since July 2013, made daily work plans for employees, conducted training.

May 2006 - Mar 2010

AUTO MECHANIC/CAR AND SPECIAL EQUIPMENT SERVICE